https://www.kidslandusa.com/privacy-policy/

My Shopping Bag(0)
Terms & Conditions
At Kidslandusa.com, your privacy and security is paramount to the continuous on going relationship with you, our customers. We respect and understand your concern for privacy and one of our missions is to ensure that all information you choose to share with us is handled in the most safe and responsible manner. We have undertaken to create a safe online environment and implemented security standards to establish a comfortable and safe shopping environment you deserve.
Kidslandusa.com continuously gathers online customer activity and information in order to make the necessary enhancements for improving the online shopping experience of our users. Your personal information such as name, address, telephone number, credit card number, and e-mail address, which then are collected allow us to achieve this objective. Furthermore, as an official company policy, Kidslandusa.com does not under any circumstance sell or divulges its customer information to any third party.
We protect your information by storing it on a secure web server in a private database. Periodically, Kidslandusa.com sends e-mail messages containing specials offering, sales and promotions to the members on our mailing list. However, if you wish to opt out or unsubscribe from receiving e-mail communication from Kidslandusa.com or wish to be taken off the mailing list, you may do so by changing your status on our website or by contacting us through e-mail at customerservice@Kidsland.com.
Here are ways we gather information and how we use it;
Orders
While ordering our products we request the following personal information from you on our registration form: first and last name, billing/shipping address, telephone number, email address, username, password, password hint, credit card, and credit card number. This is the information we need to process your order. Your telephone number is required to complete the registration or order process, so that we can use it to contact you about your order if we need to. Your billing information is also used to ensure that the right person is charged for the merchandise ordered.
Cookies & Submissions
Cookies are small bits of electronic information that a web site can transfer to your hard drive to keep records of your visit. The use of cookies is standard on the Internet and many of the websites. At Kidslandusa.com, we use cookies as a tool to personalize your online shopping experience and assess our efforts to provide an easier, more streamlined online shopping experience. For example, cookies can be utilized to recognize you as a repeat customer each time you visit our site; it allows us to retrieve your order history and personal information so you do not have to re-enter it every time you shop. This means you can store items in your shopping bag between visits and maintain your very own special events calendar and address book. Another cookie lets us know what pages you visit as well as your browsing, shopping, and searching patterns. This enables us to identify ways to customize our online shopping environment to the preferences of our customers.
You have the option to refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser. However, if you disable the cookies, you may not be able to place or track an order (see the Help section of your browser for instructions on how to disable cookies). Should you choose to disable cookies and cannot place an order on our site; you can always place the order by phone with our Customer Service Representatives.
We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. Some of our business partners use cookies on our site. We have no access to or control over these cookies. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by Kidslandusa.com only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.
Disclosure to Authorities
Kidslandusa.com fully cooperates with law enforcement agencies working to identify those who may use our services for illegal activity. Accordingly, we reserve the right to disclose any and all information to lawful government bodies or officials under certain circumstances as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate, in connection with an investigation of fraud or other activity that is illegal or may expose us to legal liability.
Children's Privacy
In accordance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998, Kidslandusa.com's website or any of its contents are not directed towards children and do not knowingly collect personal information from children. Kidslandusa.com is concerned with safeguarding children's privacy on the internet. If we receive knowledge that a child has registered without her or his parent or guardian's permission, we will remove all personal information about that person from our files.
Secure Shopping By using our website, you consent to the usage and collection of information from you by Kidslandusa.com. Any revisions or changes made to our Privacy Policy will be posted on our website for view in order that our users are informed of what information we collect, how it is used and under what circumstance, if any, is disclosed.
Access to Personally Identifiable Information
If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, delete or deactivate it by making the change on our member information page or by emailing our Customer Support at info@kidslandusa.com or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below.
Your consent
Kidslandusa.com wants to make sure that our customers will undergo the most secure and risk-free possible online shopping experience and we want you to have as much faith in the security of your transaction as you do with our products and services. To this end, we have implemented several programs to ensure that you feel comfortable and satisfied to purchase our products.
Kidslandusa.com guarantees that any sensitive information provided by the customer is protected online; all of your transactions completed through Kidslandusa.com go through security methods to ensure that your personal information is protected. All your information (such as credit card number or address) is transmitted using secure socket layers (SSL) encryption at 128 bits (the current industry standard) to communicate securely without risk of manipulation, impersonation or tampering of sensitive personal information. We utilize this encryption during the online checkout process, including the acceptance of your credit card information, and the management of your account. Furthermore, as a company policy, we believe in guarding your personal information not only online but offline as well. As such, access to your personal information is limited only to the staff required to fulfill the duties related to your account, for instance, order fulfillment, billing and the servers, hard drive and file cabinets that store your sensitive and personal data are placed in a secured and safe setting away from possibility of incursion.
What's more, every transaction you make with us comes with a fraudulent charge protection. In general, under federal law, you will not be liable for more than $50 of fraudulent charges. In the unlikely event that you are charged, we will reimburse you up to $50, provided these fraudulent charges were made without your knowledge and consent as a result of shopping at Kidslandusa.com. All in all, we trust you will undergo a safe and secure shopping experience with us as we have taken significant measures in protecting your identity and security.
Changes in this Privacy Statement
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.
We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our website.
Should you have any questions regarding our Privacy Policy, please contact us;
*Stay up-to-date with New Product Releases, Exclusive Discounts, and Kidsland Sponsored Events
Copyright © 2020 Kidsland. All Rights Reserved.
